Software Engineer Sergei Chudov

Introduction

I'm a software engineer with 4+ years of experience. Now I am in Yerevan and ready for relocation or remote job. Currently I am learning new technologies, improving my knowledge in software development and learning English.

Contact Information

• Email address: chudov42@gmail.com

• LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/window-generator

• Github: github.com/WindowGenerator

• Phone: +37491186658

• Telegram: @WindowGenerator

Work Experience

Software Engineer

Bostongene, Yerevan, Armenia – (Jun 2022 - Present)

- Full-stack engineer. My general role is supporting, designing and implementing healthcare projects.
- Responsibilities:
 - Improve code quality
 - Participate in the creation of new projects
 - Perform algorithms
 - Construct data pipelines
 - Implement frontend/backend part of projects

- Write helm charts and concourse pipelines for projects
- Discuss with clients about product features
- Stack:
 - Python (FastAPI, SQLAlchemy)
 - Linux
 - TypeScript, Javascript, React
 - Docker, Kubernetes, Helm, Concourse
 - RabbitMQ, Redis, PostgreSQL, Neo4j

Software Engineer

USSC Ldt., Yekaterinburg, Russia – (Oct 2019 - Mar 2022)

- Participated in the development of a product aimed at ensuring the safety of factories
- Responsibilities:
 - Designed microservices in python
 - Optimized SQL in MySQL, PostgreSQL
 - Developed and supported of authorization
 - Wrote Docker images to build from source
 - Edited frontend when I didn't want to distract the frontend developers
- Stack:
 - Python (aiohttp, FastAPI, Flask, SQLAlchemy)
 - Linux
 - Docker, Jenkins
 - TypeScript, Angular

Trainee ML Engineer

NPO Avtomatiki, Yekaterinburg, Russia - (Mar 2019 - May 2019)

- I implemented prototype of system that allows you to identify people with high accuracy in real time, the data is created by a video camera.
- Responsibilities:
 - Trained additional parts of YOLOV3 model
 - Optimized of YOLOV3 performance on weak hardware
 - Selected a ML model for object recognition
- Stack:
 - Python, tensorflow, keras, sklearn, Multiprocessing on Python

Skills

Development

Python - FastAPI - aiohttp - Flask - Docker - Kubernetes - Concouse - Linux - asyncio - MySQL - PostgreSQL - Redis - RabbitMQ - Elasticsearch - Neo4j - Typescript - Angular - React

Development in Free Time

golang - rust - wasm - minecraft plugins - etcd - solidity - weird bots - ML -computer vision - AR

Contributions

- aio-pika
- ruff
- chat-langchain

Languages

Russian

Native speaker

English

В1

Education

Ural State Technical University

(Bachelor of Science (Unfinished))

Sep 2015 - Oct 2017 Radiophysicist

(Bachelor of Engineering)

Oct 2017 - Jul 2020 Design and Technology of Electronic Facilities

Coursera

Aug 2020 - Aug 2020 Algorithms, Part I Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 Introduction to Machine Learning